you know, not to be overly dramatic or
cryptic, you know, not that I would ever
do either. Uh, but I suggest that you
guys take a look around. Take a good
look at those around you because one of
you is next.
Danny,
>> that's not good to bring up at review
time.
>> Next,
>> think of this um as uh what is it? The
50th season of Survivor.
>> Yes.
>> Where are we going with this
>> now? I have Danny's attention.
>> Yes.
>> Darren Urban Ollie podcast.
>> Oh my gosh. It was such a good episode.
I have so much to catch you up on Paul
last week.
>> What's not good is that last week our
Jim Alahundra was hit by a water pump
calamity.
>> Yesterday Kasa Galvesi a water heater
disaster. It's currently Hot Springs
Calvisi. And um these things happen in
threes. And there are three of you left.
Between Cody, Danny, and Darren, one of
you is next.
>> I mean, it should be good for me that
I'm the only one not in the house.
Correct.
>> Yeah, because if you have a problem, you
just call somebody, right?
>> Yeah.
>> I mean, I guess technically so would I,
but like I would have to pay for it and
you would not.
>> I don't know. The karma gods are now on
alert for what Danny just said right
there. She was trying to deflect and uh
I think maybe she might be in the
crosshairs now.
>> Does it have to be a water heater?
>> No, [laughter] I'm just saying. or just
calamity
>> just just some sort of significant
costly fix is straight ahead in your
future.
>> Not quite the same thing and and
actually there was a happy ending
>> headache El Grande
>> for me.
>> Okay. But this weekend, uh, my wife is
out of town and so I decided to take a
solo trip up to Flagstaff on Friday
night and through Saturday until Sunday
morning because I wanted to just go
hiking kind of like be one with nature,
Paul, because that's who I am. And uh,
>> are you taking Jake Plumber?
>> And was your work laptop out in nature
with you?
>> No.
>> Oh, no. I I actually I I think I set a
record mentally for least amount of time
thinking about work, which I that's hard
for me to do. Um,
>> Henry Darren Thorough.
>> But I was out and I was hiking around in
the Coconino forest and I had at one
point there there was like this dirt
road and I pulled off to park my car and
then I went hiking and I'm thinking,
okay, I know where I blah blah blah
blah. And then I got far enough or I
started realizing
I might not know where I am. [laughter]
>> That's a bad feeling. Now, I will say
that I'm somewhat comfortable in
Flagstaff, having spent I I lived there
a year and a half. We I spent a year of
my life in NA dorms with 12 training
camps. This is where Cardinals
Underground originally started. Paul,
you're well aware of that.
>> But when I was kind of out in the middle
of the forest there,
>> any moment now, by the way, the garbage
truck will come by the dorm. Go ahead.
>> There was like there was there was a
good 20 minutes. There was a moment
where in my head I thought to myself,
well, it's it's only like 12:15 in the
afternoon. I have water. I have a
jacket. If things get really dire, I'm
not going to die out here. And then
>> where's my Rambo knife?
>> I decided uh I and I didn't have it
didn't have internet. It because you're
in the middle of the forest.
>> You're not going to survive that
obviously. No internet.
>> But so I I couldn't get the maps.
But I what I found out was even without
internet, your phone still can find your
parked car.
And thank the Lord for that because I
was able to generally get back towards
my car and that's how I found my way
back.
>> Okay.
>> Amazing.
>> All right. I mean, you know, Gen Z
wouldn't have made it. I mean, you know,
they don't have Google Maps to get
navigate back.
>> Tik Toks about being lost in the forest.
It wasn't. So, it not a calamity like
you had, Paul. But but you are always
sure where you were
>> at least.
>> Okay.
>> I'm just hoping Paul has found a way to
to shower if he doesn't have water at
his house. But you're the one closest to
him, Darren. So,
>> more your problem than mine.
>> Yeah, it was a uh what I call a Santa
Cruz shower. Monterey Bay about 50° this
morning. Jumping in.
>> That'll wake you right up.
>> Did not need coffee this morning. That
is for sure. Uh you know what we do need
before we move forward? We need to learn
from the past. Darren's episode included
out of context. Here we go.
>> Please tell me you're clipping that. You
have to clip that one.
>> Can we have like an outof context
blooper wheel or something?
>> Can I just ask AI? Sorry, Darren. I just
asked the following question.
>> Can't spell Calhesi without AI. So,
>> feeling good about myself, everybody.
>> That's what's important here.
>> The coffee helped.
>> Okay. Can I
>> bring in the energy?
>> You know what? If I just bring up Mike
Tyson's butt, I just know I'm going to
get some out of Paul.
>> Clip. Clip. Clip. If I can give any word
of advice to whoever that ex-girlfriend
is or any listeners we have, I'm going
to look into my camera right here. They
never change. Do not take him back and
do not fall for it. Whoop to freaking
do, Darren. Whoa. Unprecedented.
>> Wow. As I look over here,
>> he's really smelling himself.
>> We don't want to count any [music]
chickens prior to hatching.
>> He's getting a little too hotty.
>> He was popping bottles. [music]
>> Flumxed, flabbergasted.
Great googly moogly.
>> Not I. I don't ever mail it in.
>> I I think you're you're smart. I mean,
if you
>> me Thank you.
>> You're the queen is what you are. I'm
just some schmuck. He did it. He threw
the sandwich.
>> Criminal misuse of an Italian grinder.
>> Leroy Jens.
>> Tough tiddly wings. Thank you, Danny.
>> You have no idea how lucky you truly
are.
>> Wow, that's awful arrogant of you, Paul.
>> That's what she said.
Well, Darren was energetic to begin
that.
>> I don't remember like half of [laughter]
those.
>> More than half of those.
>> And uh Oh, boy. Okay. Um
I'm I'm distracted also by the Barry
Sanders highlights over here considering
I was on the sideline for half of those
runs, but that's another story. The um
>> working in Chicago, Paul, you were
working in Chicago, correct?
>> Uh I was actually Chicago and uh and
Michigan. Yes. So that's true. So there
you go. Yeah, it's uh so you've seen
plenty of Bears Lions.
>> Yes, I have. And uh and I saw the uh
Brett Favre touchdown pass to a wideopen
Sterling Sharp that won a playoff game
right on the sidelines in Pontiac,
Michigan, too. But that's uh by the way,
speaking of uh all-time great receivers,
Frank Sanders earlier today happened to
agree with me, Danny.
>> Whoa.
>> On a certain draft related possibility,
>> Sunny Styles
>> that we will get to [laughter] a little
bit. Did I telegraph that? Was that was
that as obvious as as uh By the way,
Frank Sanders brought up Sunny Styles on
his own. [laughter] It had nothing to do
with me. It had nothing to do with me.
Although, I have to say, as we segue
into what free agency means for the
draft, uh I guess the signing of the
linebacker from New England, right, Jack
Gibbons two-year deal, I guess, would
say otherwise as to taking an inside
linebacker. Maybe, just maybe, don't
know. But you need uh obviously you need
look if we learned one thing on defense
a year ago and there were a lot of
lessons learned last year on a lot of
different fronts. You need significant
proven reliable depth at inside
linebacker.
>> Paul, don't let that free agency signing
get in the way of dreaming your dreams.
Weren't you the one who said if you
could go back and you could draft a Hall
of Fame linebacker, you would in the
first round.
>> Sure. If it's if the guy's name is Fred
Warner or Luke Keequley and is three too
high for Fred Warner or Luke Keequley,
absolutely not. It's not even a hot
take. What am I doing?
>> I mean, Keequley's like five years
removed from playing, so it's probably a
little high right now.
>> He's going into the Hall of Fame with
Larry Fitzgerald.
>> Yes, that's all I'm saying.
>> And he's not coming back out. All I'm
saying is what Frank Sanders was saying
is I'm now deflecting you know the focus
off yours truly and uh you know and the
glare because it's getting pretty bright
at this point. But if you have that guy
playing that position and he's dynamic
and he's sideline to sideline and he's
legitimately running that four sub four
five as an inside backer then yes that
has the potential to change your defense
significantly.
>> Again why let this stop you from
dreaming your dreams? You can move M.
Wilson Senior back out as your will
linebacker if you've got Sunny Styles
inside.
>> And how often did Kyle Vandenbos and Rob
Frederickson talk about M. Wilson senior
off the edge is a re was a really good
competitive advantage for this Cardinal
defense two years ago.
>> Here's my question about Sunny Styles.
And I'm not going to disagree. If you
think you can get Patrick Willis at
three like
>> Thank you. That's a good one.
>> Fine. Patrick Willis and Navaro Bowman.
Remember that back in the day?
>> Yeah, I do remember that, unfortunately.
But here's my question, Paul. Would you
be saying the same thing about Sunny
Styles if he hadn't dressed up in a
t-shirt and shorts and done a bunch of
cool things for a day in Indianapolis?
>> Look, I I get it. The measurables were
through the roof. There's no doubt about
it.
>> Were you thinking this when Texas Tech
was playing this year?
>> Okay. So,
>> or is he Texas Tech? He's Ohio State.
>> Ohio State. Ohio State. I I didn't watch
much Ohio State. Um, and honestly, it
wasn't it wasn't as much the
measurables, although they were
extraordinary.
>> He set a few records for the position.
It really was the way everyone was
talking about him. It were were the
analysts. It was the Daniel Jeremiah,
some of the other draft analysts. You
guys were there, the manner in which
they have described him and assessed his
skill set and and and he's not a
tweener. This is an Arbell Ree where
you're wondering is he inside, is he off
the edge, is he an outside backer, where
is he? No.
>> Wait a minute. Was was that a was that a
Zen Collins Isaiah Simmons comment?
>> Hassan Reic Buchanan. Just beware anyone
high in the draft who doesn't have a
definitive position.
>> I do like the pick of Styles the further
you drop down. Now, he you you're not
probably going to get outside the top 10
and still get styles. But if the
Cardinals do trade down from three,
let's say somebody really wants to take,
I don't know, running back Jeremiah Love
away from Tennessee at four. Ding.
>> Or you have a very specific edge rusher
you want or an offensive tackle that you
want.
>> There are still options at three. I
don't expect to see a lot of trades,
especially because it is a low
quarterback draft and that's typically
the positions people trade up for. It's
a possibility and I think the further
you drop down from three, the chances
rise of taking that linebacker.
>> I will say that as we get closer and
we're still not close, we're still more
than a month out,
>> six weeks out from the draft,
>> whatever it is. I I've noticed on some
of these lists like even the top usually
the top 10 is pretty set and I feel like
it's starting to get a little more
jumbled more than it normally is at this
time of year. usually you know what who
a top one of the top 10 guys is going to
be. Like I've seen the the Malinoa pick
which obviously a lot of people like to
mock to the Cardinals at three. I saw
something the other day that had him as
the third tackle going in the first
round.
>> That was I believe Mel Kyper's most
recent mock draft.
>> Wow. I thought Spencer Feno was the guy
who really dropped to the Monroe free
Georgia kid was is all of a sudden mo
moving up quote unquote
>> right without having played a game.
>> Right. How much of that is real? How
much of that is smoke screens?
>> Yeah, it's But but to Danny's point,
could you trade out of number three to
the back half of the top 10 and still
get that tackle?
>> Still get Sunny Styles. You're not going
to get David Bailey or Arl Reese at that
point?
>> Probably not. But see, I feel like at
this point,
>> the same reason that
>> you might get Ruben Bane.
>> I think that you're willing to do that
is the same reason they're not going to
be able to do that. Because the reason
you're willing to do that is because
there's going to be these really good
players about the same level at 10 as
there is at three. And so why would you
trade up?
>> Jeremiah Love, that's got to be the only
reason to to your point. It's the only
reason. There just has to be that. I
mean, what other running back is in this
draft in the last few drafts that's been
as dynamic as Jeremiah
>> Love? I guess I I see it as like I feel
like in some ways the people that want
to be able to put some kind of
excitement in the top round of the draft
with potential trades, they know they
can't do it with a quarterback. So the
only possible guy you could do it with
would be Jeremiah Love. And I just don't
buy that somebody's going to trade up to
get him. Not that high. I just don't I
don't buy it.
>> Let's do a lightning round through some
of the free agent signings that that
we've had. All right. So we talked about
Jack Gibbons last couple years. Well,
last year with New England. Before that,
he had 28 starts with Tennessee. And
it's interesting because he's been
productive. 63 242 age 27. Four years in
the league. Last year, he started a
bunch of games, including the Super Bowl
for New England, had 71 tackles. You
know, he's played a lot of special teams
as well. I mean, he saw action in all
four of their playoff games last year
for New England. yet he wasn't tendered
as a restricted free agent by Tennessee
two years ago and then this offseason
was not tendered by New England. So what
does that mean? I don't know.
Opportunity for the Cardinals to bring
on Jack Gibbons.
>> A quick quick sideline on not being
tendered.
When you're talking about not being
tender, that means they're a restricted
free agent. the way the tender offers
have grown in terms of what how much you
have to pay a guy for one year now to
get a tender offer. Most of even if a
team wants a guy back, usually it's not
worth tendering him anymore. So that in
itself to me doesn't mean you don't
necessarily want the guy. Now that
doesn't mean New England did want him
back. Um and obviously they didn't pay
as much or they weren't willing to pay
as much as the Cardinals were, but and
and maybe some of it had to do with uh a
potential playing time here. I don't
know.
>> Andrew Billings from the Bears most
recently, age 31, 61, 340. This dude
looks like the epitome of a nose tackle.
Combined with Roy Lopez, you're you're
you're you're going to be stuffing the A
gaps with those two guys. Dvin Tomlinson
is out. In fact, DT signed with the
Chargers, right?
>> Yes.
>> Okay. So, and that a lot of that was
capomics and he was due a big number.
And so you go ahead and you get Billings
at age 31 on a one-year deal. You get
Roy Lopez on a on a two-year deal. And
and uh but I I feel pretty good about
the interior. If you can plug and play,
and I do mean plug those two guys in,
and then you have Darius Robinson and
Walter Nolan on either side. Okay. I
think that's the vision, right?
>> It is a vision. It needs to pay off. You
need to see more, especially from the
last two names that you mentioned. need
to see a healthy Walter Nolan who looked
fantastic in the few opportunities he
had as a rookie. And this is your three
for Darius Robinson. You need to see him
one out on the field consistently
staying healthy and two he would
probably tell you the same thing. You
need more production out of him.
Whatever that's going to be, however
they're going to use him, wherever
they're going to place him with some of
these additional signings, you need more
out of your first round pick. That that
that's just what it comes down to is
needing more production. I like this
signing of you're losing your run
stuffer and Tomlinson and you replace
him there. And I also think it's an
interesting note of he was Chicago's
2024 Walter Payton man of the year
nominee. So that that good culture fit.
And there's a question we haven't really
brought up on this podcast mostly
because we don't know is there is a lot
of question marks around Klay's
Campbell. Is he going to play for year
19? Is he going to play year 19 if he is
with the Cardinals? Right. So, it kind
of feels like some of these decisions
are also being made in in the case that
you are without Campbell.
>> I am going to bring up because that was
a question in the mailbag this week. I
know more and more people are going to
wonder.
>> Spoilers. I haven't read it yet.
>> Oh, sorry. Um, but like with Campbell
one, I would think he would make a
decision before the draft, not just if
he wanted to come back here, but if he
wants to be anywhere because you you got
to let teams understand where they stand
with the roster. And two, uh, last year
when he ended up agreeing to terms with
the Cardinals, it was because I remember
it very distinctly, I was on a flight
back from the owner's meetings, and the
owner's meetings are coming up in a
couple weeks. So maybe we're getting
close to where Kas Campbell might say
something about what his future might
be.
>> Oh, maybe Kas just shows up since it's
at the Builtmore and just sort of works
the room, if you will. Kind of comes out
and see, you know, see who's interested.
I'll just say this, based on the visuals
and the optics of him sort of soaking in
those last couple games, I'd be
surprised. I'd be surprised. I know
nothing on the inside. It's just a gut
feel. It's just an observation.
>> I just remember him saying to me that
when he finished 2020, well, this was
five. When he finished 2023 and 2024,
he felt the exact same way in his last
game.
>> Okay. and then he ended up watching the
playoffs and the Super Bowl and he
started getting revved up again and
that's why he came back. If you go uh
NFL films did a piece on him uh
>> at the end of the 24 season before he
came to play for the Cardinals and there
was a couple of behind the scenes where
he's like this is my last year and they
showed him walking off the field in New
York against the Jets and that was a guy
who was taking it all in because he
wasn't going to play again and then he
played again. So what's crazy too is
something that he was very forthcoming
about was he wants it to be on his
terms. Campbell doesn't Campbell doesn't
want another team to make the decision
for him. I.e. nobody wants to sign him
or he ends up getting cut. But when
you're looking at the numbers, he was
arguably your most productive well he
was your most productive defensive
lineman, one of your most productive
defenders on the field last year. So
it's not to say that if he didn't put in
the work you would be thinking, can he
still do this? Because he just proved
that he could. It's a matter of does he
want to and put his body through
everything he'd have to starting right
now in the offseason.
>> Well, and and that's part I mean if you
if you go back like
>> the Cardinals weren't the only team that
was trying to get him last year. It was
like six or seven teams including the
Chiefs, including the Eagles. It wasn't
like
>> the Ravens really wanted him. We learned
later.
>> So, like we'll see. It'll be interesting
to see what he decides to do. And I and
I hope unlike other people who have
retired and then not said they were
retired around this team, I would hope
that if he does decide to retire, he
actually tells people so we can talk.
>> So you don't get emails about it every
week.
>> Yeah, that'd be nice.
Um, we had the pleasure of meeting
Andrew Wingard, the uh former
Jacksonville safety, seven years with
the Jags, and he comes on board with a
reported one-year deal. So Jaylen
Thompson has gone to Dallas. So JT made
over 9 million last year and so Dewey as
they call him comes on board a reported
three to four million somewhere in there
and uh and we'll see he seems highly
motivated.
>> I don't want to I don't I no I'm
laughing because I I don't want to put
him in this box so to speak right off
the bat but Dennis Gard 2.0 No, I mean
he told us the nickname Jacksonville.
>> He he said when the two of them saw each
other for the first time in the
Jacksonville facility, they literally
paused and pointed at each other and
like looking in the mirror. A big a big
time player, a big playmaker on special
teams. And I mean that in with the
highest regard of of Dennis Gard 2.0.
Well, it's just you look, two guys who
weren't drafted, two guys who earned
every single snap that they've received
in the NFL, two guys who have hair out
the back of the helmet and it's on fire
at the same time. That's the way they
play. And and he he seems to have a
little bit of a chip on his shoulder
pad. doesn't like a lot of the um he
feels like he's been misrepresented as
not being athletic enough in coverage to
not be a complete safety that he's only
a box safety you know just some crazy
guy out throw his self you know after a
ball carrier against the run so um it
was it was very interesting he he's got
a great personality and he's been doing
this seven years and so and you know the
number of comparisons that he gets
everything from Pat Tilman to Gard to
the Dewey, you know, I mean, just um
it's just interesting like as I was sort
of joking that the personalities of
Kendrick Bourne and Gardenner Mchu are
going to get us through a long preseason
with the extra preseason game. Uh throw
Dwey into the mix as well. He's going to
be a go-to in the locker room for a lot
of quotes. So, there's that. Let's see
what else did they end up Well, then
they got Devin Duivere, the return man.
That's still not official as we record
this, but I'm fairly certain that that
will become official. And that probably
means I'm assuming they're going to
probably move on from Greg Dorch
bringing in a Duiverade to who's been an
allp pro return man and has done really
well both on punt and kick returns this
in his career.
>> Cardinals brought back wide receiver
Simei Foko. That's a big a big retainer
on special teams. Somebody who had his
year cut short last year with some
injury. And Kendrick Borne is not not
just a great personality, but but
that'll be he'll be fighting for that
spot of the number three receiver.
Doesn't have a ton of special teams
experience, so he won't likely play a
role as large there as Foko or Du Renee
would. That that'll mostly be your third
option out wide. May maybe go deep every
now and then, but I mean Borne told me
he likes doing the quote dirty work. He
likes blocking. He likes being in the
middle of the field doing those kinds of
things.
>> So what all these signings mean so far
for the draft?
If anything,
>> I mean, I I think it the whole point of
free agency, and I'm a believer in this,
and I do believe for the most part, this
is what teams trying to do. You try and
plug holes the best you can. It doesn't
necessarily mean you're signing a guy
that's going to be a 10-year starter at
whatever position he plays,
but it gives you an option. for
instance, and I've had this come up a
bunch of times, and I understand that
not everybody's happy with like
necessarily the Mchu signing. Okay. All
right. I understand that. I'm not saying
he's going to be your long-term guy, but
let's say you're going into this draft
and and I don't know, but I'm Let me
just throw some names out there. Let's
say you like Tai Simpson and uh this is
this is for Zack Drew Aller and you
don't like any of the other quarterbacks
and Tai Simpsons off the board before
you get a chance to get him in the
second round or trade up into the first,
whatever. By the way, the latest Mel
Kyper has the Jets trading back into the
middle of the first round and taking Tai
Simpson.
>> And then Aller is the other guy you
like. And for whatever reason, you're
thinking you're going to be able to grab
him with a fifth round pick and for some
reason somebody takes him in the fourth
round that nobody really expected. Okay.
Well, you've covered your bases at
quarterback then if you didn't draft a
guy. Uh because what? No offense to
Katon Slovis, but you probably don't
want Kedon Slovis as your full-time
backup for this whole year. And and I
think that's kind of how it is. The
Sunny Styles thing is a great example. I
I know there are people out there
talking about, well, since they signed
Gibbons, there's no way. You were joking
about it like there's no way they'll
take St. I don't believe that.
>> I don't believe that either.
>> I mean, you're if you really believe
he's that guy, then you're going to take
him and you work with it.
>> Elijah Wilkinson at right tackle. So now
at least you have a guy who started all
17 games for the Falcons last year at
right tackle just in case dot dot dot.
You don't get that franchise right
tackle. You're not going to be able to
get every position that you want in the
draft that's going to be able to plug
and play right away. So, you you better
cover yourself roster-wise in case one
of these positions you aren't able to
address.
It's pretty simple.
It's not rocket science.
>> Did you get new glasses frames?
>> I did.
>> I like them. I like the color.
>> I appreciate it.
>> Light the lamp, Paul. [laughter]
>> Sorry. I'm just I was noticing while you
were going on your rant.
>> Yes. If that doesn't intrigue everyone
to watch video, if you're only listening
to audio, I don't know what will.
>> By the way, Gardenner Menchure reported
one year, six million or so.
>> Uh I think it was five and seven.
>> I think it was around
>> I think I think he and Jacob and this is
the other thing about the quarterback.
I've also heard
they won't won't take a quarterback now
because they signed Gardner Mchu, which
is ridiculous. You have you have about
11 or 12 million dollars you're paying
to brassette and mince you together.
You're not going to take a quarterback
at number three with where everything
stands. So it's easily affordable to
take a second round or beyond
quarterback. Put them in the room.
You're living the New York Giants 2025
life with Jameus Winston and Russell
Wilson and Jackson Dart. And yeah,
you'll have a couple of veteran
quarterbacks, but you'll have a rookie
that you can work with and you can you
can play the depth chart because it's
not like you're you're getting killed.
And yes, I understand that they are
going to ultimately have Kyler Murray on
the cap this year for about $48 million.
They were already going to have him on
the cap for 55 if he was here. So, you
already were accounting for that money
one way or the other. I know he's not
here anymore, but that was already part
of the cap calculations anyways. You
know, it's been interesting to me when
we talk about the quarterback situation
is online.
I I felt like the minor minority in that
I was not surprised that the Cardinals
are seemingly rolling with set moving
forward after moving on from Kyler
Murray. I can understand if fans maybe
wanted a a name that was floating around
free agency, somebody who signed
elsewhere, but I I've been a little
confused at the people who have
seemingly been surprised that this is
the move the Cardinals are going in when
Brett's here already under contract.
He's familiar with this team. He might
not be familiar with Mike Lafleur, per
se, but he's been in the league for 10
years. And and and I'm not here to, you
know, cushion any stats, but let's
remember that majority of the games that
Brassette was playing, he had an
incredibly banged up offensive line. At
one point was down to a six and seven
string running backs, and at one point
had one healthy wide receiver in
addition to Trey McBride. Now, I'm not
saying he's a Kyler Murray by any means.
I've just been surprised at the amount
of people who are seemingly surprised
that the Cardinals are taking the route,
you know, when you're taking everything
into consideration with the finances of
moving on from Murray of building the
foundation with the offensive line and
some of the other pieces around and and
continuing with a quarterback they feel
comfortable with. That's been a little
shocking to me that people people have
this perception that this is a lastm
minute scramble and and this was never a
possibility when I think this was a
strong possibility from the beginning.
Remember, no offense threw more passes
and attempted fewer rushes than the
Arizona Cardinals because of the injury
situation, the O line, the running back
room because those games got lopsided
and they got behind so quickly in so
many games down the stretch. The old
saying that a run game is a
quarterback's best friend. Jacobe
Brassette was awful lonely last year. If
that's the case, that's all I'm going to
say about that. And by the way, the fact
Brassette is on this roster actually to
me enhances the chances that you're
going to draft a quarterback because is
there a better mentor veteran
quarterback to work with to bring a
rookie in than to learn behind and under
Jacobe Brassette?
>> No way. So to me, I mean, I could sit
here and I could go hot take and I could
fan the flames of the fact Aaron Rogers
has yet to sign and Nathaniel Hackett is
on this staff and what are the odds that
>> Aaron
>> Oh, brother.
>> All right, save me. Let's get cultured.
How about that? Let's do it.
>> Let's do it.
>> Okay.
>> Uh Danny, we'll segue to you.
>> Getting cultured with Danny. It is not
just directed at Paul.
>> Am I the default uncultured Philistine
around here? Yes. You got me very
excited. Now
>> I am on social media and consume more
pop culture than both of you combined.
>> I think I'm being unfairly profiled, but
go ahead.
>> Let's go.
March Madness officially begins today.
The first game at 3:40 p.m. Mountain
Standard Time. Did either of you make a
bracket?
>> I have not done a bracket since the late
90s.
>> You could have just said no.
>> That's not true. No.
>> No fun league over here. Darren Irving,
>> I I I
>> You're in the 99.9th percentile of
basketball fans. You haven't done a
bracket in 25 plus years.
>> Correct.
>> Why?
>> Cuz I just have no interest in it
anymore. And being an old school college
basketball person, it it was I mean
obviously I haven't done it for a long
time. Way well predating this, but like
I know nothing about college basketball.
Same. It's funny. No, it's no fun.
>> Paul, did you make a bracket?
>> All I know is Cal Baptist is in and Cal
Berkeley is not. Other than that, I
mean,
>> so did you root for Cal VC Baptist?
>> You can cheer for Missou. I'm going to
get I might have to do that. Uh I'm
going to get I'm going to get roped in
at some point. Yeah,
>> I made a bracket. I went through it
pretty quickly. Uh we'll see how I do. I
did come in second and our our bracket
challenge within our department last
year.
>> If you were like me earlier in the week,
you had a split screen on your TV
watching the World Baseball Classic at
the same time as the Oscars. WC finals
are tonight. US First Venezuela.
Speaking of the Oscars though, Michael
B. Jordan took home the Oscar for best
actor for Sinners where he played twins.
I'm not a big horror movie fan, but I I
did see that movie and I enjoyed it. And
I learned that you can have a tie. There
was a tie for liveaction short film.
>> Y there was a tie and I guess it was
planned.
>> I did see Michael.
>> Is that like when Fitz and Eli tied for
man of [laughter] the year in the NFL?
>> That's right. How about Michael B.
Jordan walking into the In-N-Out Burger
with a statue? Oh man, that was good. I
mean, how can you not think of Friday
Night Lights, right? That's your
football connection. He was the uh
quarterback for the East Dylan,
whatever. You know,
>> I never watched that show.
>> Great show. I'm actually really excited
about this next little sub section we
have of getting cultured. It's It's been
on my mind for the last few weeks cuz
I've been seeing pictures on my Twitter.
To celebrate nearing the end of spring
training and getting towards the
beginning of the regular baseball
season, I'm going to share some
interesting food options at ballparks
around the country. And I would love to
know if the two of you would be willing
to try them. And I I don't really have
photos, so I'm going to do my best with
my descriptions. You ready?
>> Here we go.
>> First stop, the Hartford Yard Goats and
what they are calling the anti-hero.
It's a grilled two-foot allbeef hot dog
with 11 powdered donuts around the hot
dog in the bun and it's topped with a
mustard ketchup drizzle and sweet candy
pink and [music] blue sprinkles on an
artisan Italian loaf bun. That was a lot
of words, but it's pretty much a hot dog
with some powdered donuts around it. H
>> how can you have the ketchup and mustard
with the donuts?
>> I mean, I also I also would not try. I
assume we're all all together on that
one. Sorry to do this to you, Paul, but
now we're going to Seattle. The Mariners
have an incredible Washington State
ferryboat souvenir. You have multiple
options to it's it's a physical boat.
Like instead of a helmet, it's a ferry
boat that they're putting the food in.
And some of your options include loaded
crab nachos, Old Bay fries, chicken
tenders, and more. And it's all in a
ferry boat.
>> Why not just call it a trough at that
point? Honestly, you know,
>> pretty much all those things that that I
mean,
these better be termed sharables because
if one person's eating them, you
>> I'm guessing the marketing the strategy
is you you put that stand right next to
the beer stand because you you got to
you have to have a few in you before you
go order that.
>> I would for sure try that though.
Seattle also has an adorable chocolate
moose mousse. It's soft serve in a
souvenir helmet, but they have a cookie
with the moose face on it. [music] It
looks really cute. And I did see
actually online on Tuesday, I guess the
Diamondbacks are doing uh they're
they're having some media out there and
sharing some new food items. And the
ones I've seen online, this one actually
sounds pretty good. A hand dipped street
corn dog. Sounds delicious, but it's too
big. It looks like two or three hot dogs
in one. They have a hand dipped chili
cheese corn dog and what they're calling
a 50/50 stretch. It's a massive sandwich
that is half chicken parm hot [music]
half hot pastrarami.
>> Now I'm in. You saved the best for last.
Best for last right there. There you go.
>> Okay. Although I and this this is an
interesting note. Sunday I went to a
spring training game and there was a
woman in front I mean it was it was hot.
It was probably 92 degrees. Sun was
blaring down.
>> Eat right now. God dang it. And there
was a woman in front of me and the food
she decided to eat was [music] like a
baked potato with what looked like a
year bowl. I'm like, "What are you?" And
she ate some of it and then she put it
aside for a few minutes and then she
continued eating it. And I'm thinking,
if that did not make your stomach hurt
before, there got to be rules of what
we're selling and eating at baseball
games out in the heat.
>> Yeah, there's nothing like leaving your
lunch in the hot direct sun for a few
innings and then coming back to it. I'm
sure that's uh
>> No thank you.
>> Yeah, there's a lot of things we don't
need. The uh hottest March in Phoenix
history is right up there.
>> Unfortunately,
>> I think I I think I saw that the average
temperature in March is 78 degrees over
time. And what are we going to be? We're
going to have 103 on Thursday.
>> Unfortunately. Well, you both have been
cultured. You're welcome. See you at
Chase Field for the 50/50 stretch. Paul,
>> by the way, if those Mariner fans eat
all those desserts, they're going to be
calling them big dumper pretty soon.
Boy, it's uh I mean, it's You better be
careful up there, Marin.
>> Cody back there. And a clap from Omo.
There you go. All right, here's the
deal. Uh, my quarterback, uh, hot take
was shot down. Uh, how about former
Cardinals quarterback Kyler Murray in
Minnesota? Can Can I just make what
might qualify as as a hot take or maybe
a saw off? Maybe it's irresponsible.
It's it's just a thought more than
anything else. this whole um
narrative that you go to the Vikings and
somehow you salvage your quarterback
career. The Vikings have had nine
quarterbacks in the last five years.
Sam Darnold spent the year before
Minnesota in San Francisco. And I've
heard Darnold do interviews where he
raved about Kyle Shanahan, everything
that system and that coach did for him
before he spent the year in Minnesota
and then they let him go and he went to
Seattle and won a Super Bowl. So, I'm
getting a little, you know, what's the
list with all the things I'm tired of,
you know, like Snoop Dogg and every
single piece of content out there, you
know? I mean, just things I'm getting
tired of.
>> Ray Gun. I'm getting a little tired of
the whole Vikings is like some sort of
panacea to resurrect your quarterback
career. I think it's a little overdone
right now. Let's wait and see how this
goes with Kyler Murray.
>> I think that's fair. I think that's
absolutely fair. I did, you know, I I'm
I'm like everybody else. I'm curious to
know how this goes.
I find it interesting to a certain
extent that
a number of people that
nationally had issues with Kyler's game
um have suddenly flipped and now feel
like
everything is completely different just
because he's on a different team. Even
though at the time they were talking
about the player, not necessarily the
team he was on. I I guess we're going to
see what happens. Um,
you know, I I don't there's been reports
out there that JJ McCarthy still has a
chance to win the job. I don't see that
happening over Kyler. Um, but, you know,
I guess we'll see.
>> There's there's just recency bias,
right? And and especially as national
reporters, right, you kind of buy into
some of the excitement and that's a
talking point. I you know, it has been
interesting to kind of see online. I
mean, and and to be fair, right, the
clips they're posting are absolutely
incredible plays by Murray. It's not
like we weren't talking about those.
It's not like we weren't, you know,
praising that aspect of his game. It it
it has been an interesting
discussion um and and viewpoint of
You're right, Paul. Is Minnesota's going
and going to be the place for him to
resurrect his career, so to speak, and
and find success. And that's not to say,
you know, none of us wish him anything
other than that. Here's the three of us
on underground. It's it's just
interesting that the difference of how
people spoke about him with the
Cardinals to now with the Vikings when
he hasn't even stepped foot on the field
for them.
>> I did find it interesting. Albert
Brerier did basically a breakdown of how
he ended up in Minnesota. Um he had a
number of Eric Birkhart quotes. that's
Kyler's agent, so I'm assuming almost
all this information probably is coming
from Eric Burkheart. Um, but basically
the conversation was uh right around the
Dallas game, Kyler was still hurt, but
by the time he was going to be coming
off the IR, both sides decided it there
was it made no sense to bring him back.
I interpret that as he probably was
healthy enough to play once he came off
IR, but both sides are like, man, let's
let's just shut him down for the season.
I we've talked about that a million
times. I mean, I I I I if that had been
the case, I wish everybody would have
been a little bit more forthcoming on
some of that stuff. But regardless, um
you know, this is where it is. And I
will say this, I've said it in the
mailbag. I know I've said it before. I
know there are a lot of people that are
like, "Oh, I'm glad Kyler is not here
anymore." I know there's a lot of fans
that are like, "This is ridiculous.
Kyler Murray should still be the
quarterback.
Kyler Murray needed a fresh start. The
Cardinals needed a fresh start. This was
the right thing to do for both sides."
>> That's that's how I feel about it. And
and based off what Breer was saying in
his article with quotes from Birkhard,
if that's the case, right, then it's
everyone who's saying online all the
things they're saying about the
Cardinals quote unquote benching Kyler
Murray for Jacobe Brassette, that would
essentially negate that entire thought
process because if if they come to terms
of this is not the place for either of
us to find success in the future, then
>> right, you want to keep him healthy if
there's any possibility of of a possible
trade partner.
So was there any mention that indeed
they there were attempts to trade him
before the deadline?
>> I they didn't get into that
>> because it was right after the deadline
where then he went in
>> IR. It was a very it was a very
basically it it was just a paragraph
basically saying he tried to come back.
He was working on it. the Dallas weekend
happened and I think if I recall
correctly it said his his foot was only
about 60 or 70%
better and he didn't have a Liz Frank
injury but there was a fear that if he
tried to play on what he did have it
could turn into a Liz Frank injury which
is why they essentially decided okay
let's put him on IR and see where we are
obviously Jacobe was playing the way he
was at that point in terms of producing
and then so by the time it was I think
everybody Now, we can get into splitting
hairs and whether the Cardinals, if they
had brought him back, whether they would
have played him or if they said, "No,
you're just going to be the backup
anyways and whether Kyler would want
it." All that stuff. It's it it's a moot
point now. I mean, it might make for an
interesting 30 for30 someday, but right
now it's it's again, I I think the big
thing is both sides desperately needed
to move on from each other uh and just
kind of restart everything. And we'll
see what that means in Minnesota for
Kyler Murray. He obviously has a
one-year deal. Um there was offset
language in his in his uh contract. So,
the only way he was going to make more
than the 36.8 8 million that he was
guaranteed from the Cardinals was if
somebody was willing to pay him more
than that and nobody's going to do that
which is why he's playing for the
minimum because he couldn't have there's
no reason to pay him 20 million when the
Cardinals that just lowers what the
Cardinals owe. So he's going to play for
the minimum. Uh he's can't be tagged so
he can be a straight out free agent next
year if he plays well. I do think he'll
obviously have a market but we'll see
how that goes. And for the Cardinals,
we've we already touched on it. They're
looking for a quarterback of the future.
Uh Paul, you and I have been through
this before with this team. Kyler Murray
or not Kyler Murray, Kurt Warner retired
and then they were kind of in this limbo
because they were never quite bad enough
to get a high pick for a quarterback.
And so you kind of floundered until you
found Carson Palmer. And it'll be
interesting to see how they proceed from
here. It was kind of weird watching
Kyler Murray's introductory press
conference with Minnesota and he's in
all this purple, right? After seeing him
in all this red for all these years, you
know, it it it's when you learn things
after the fact, it it kind of clicks,
right? If you think back to certain
things and hearing what you're saying,
Darren, it makes sense why when Murray
was asked about his health and his foot
in Minnesota, his answer was more so
about the pride he takes in his rehab
and keeping his body healthy. There was
no real yes, I'm healthy. This is the
update on my foot. This is the exact
foot injury I had, which means nobody
ever really got any of that information.
It is all a moot point. Now, over the
last seven years, would both parties of
Murray and the Cardinals probably wish
they would have handled situations or
handled things they said about
situations differently? Probably. I'm
sure both sides would say yes. It is a
moot point. Now, though,
>> the point that's most relevant going
forward in my opinion, thanks for
asking, is
>> when he says in the statement, "My best
ball is ahead of me." Okay, let's see.
Let I mean, let's find out because you
can argue that his best ball was in 20
and 21.
>> Okay, I let me let me say this. Okay, I
you're not wrong. And if he's going to
say it, then then there's some
accountability for saying it. But to me,
my best ball is ahead of me is akin to
saying, uh, the surgery went successful.
Um, I'm in the best shape of my life.
>> What else is he gonna say? I I I'm I'm
going to I'm going to
>> you're going to push back.
>> I'm going to definitely push back on
that. That that to me uh translation
from media speak into uh the intention
or the intended meaning is um that prior
situation was holding me back.
>> I think okay, I'll give you that.
>> And and now um I'm going to be able to
truly blossom and flourish and take my
game to the next level. And I just don't
see there hasn't been much evidence of
that. There was the 24 season where the
Cardinals were in first place. At the
buy, they were six and four and he had
three interceptions in 10 games. And
then coming out of the buy, the final
seven games, he threw eight picks. He
ended up with 11 on the year, but eight
were after the buy and the Cardinals
lost five out of seven and obviously
fell out of the playoffs and they
haven't been the same ever since. And
neither is Kyler.
>> I find both things to be true of of both
sentiments of maybe that is what he was
intending. We don't know in his in his
post and also right that is kind of what
players say. It is kind of becoming the
NFC Northwest up there though of Drew
Peding with Detroit, Jonathan Ganon with
Green Bay and now Kyler Murray with
Minnesota. So they will all be facing
each other twice a year
>> and we'll be watching.
>> Yeah. So we'll see. But once again it's
the Vikings ninth starting quarterback
in the last five years. So, I'm curious
if whether Sam Darnold was the oneoff
and
>> and so some some of the big names though
that are out there, right, of
quarterbacks and not necessarily for
Cardinals but other teams would be Jimmy
Garopppolo, Aaron Rodgers, Kurt Cousins,
who am I forgetting?
>> I think that's probably it. And I don't
think to me at this point Garopolo is
probably going to end up back as the
Rams backup. We'll see what Rogers does.
I I heard one report today that they
think Kirk Cousins is essentially
waiting to see what Rogers does cuz he
wouldn't mind going to Pittsburgh if
Rogers doesn't go back. I'm just
curious, Paul, like I'm I'm very excited
for the pregame show when the uh the
Cardinals and the Vikings meet in the
playoffs and how you approach that the
>> NFC Championship.
>> Remember we had the vision two years
ago, Cardinals at the Lions for a
playoff game. Dang it. So, we'll see.
We'll see. Maybe you can speak it into
existence better better than I can.
Speaking of uh the NFC West related
issues and uh connections, Hollywood
Brown, former Cardinals receiver going
to the Eagles on a one-year deal
reportedly. That was interesting.
>> He had a better year with the Chiefs
than I thought. 49 catches, five
receiver, five touchdowns. I he was it
was more productive than I remembered
actually. And then Christian Kirk
reportedly coming back to the ners on a
one-year $6 million deal.
>> And then every time they talk about
Christian Kirk, they talk about the deal
he signed with Jacksonville after 2022.
Four years, 72 million he got with the
Jags.
>> He was awesome in that playoff game for
Houston, but he's unfortunately for
Christian, he's been pretty banged up.
>> Says here he's missed 18 games the past
three years
>> with Jacksonville and Houston. But yes,
in the playoffs, eight for a buck 44 and
a touchdown against Pittsburgh. And then
he had a touchdown catch against New
England. And so I mean, think of the
49ers right now. Think of Mike Evans
coming to the 49ers and saying in not so
many words. In fact, it's almost a
direct quote. The Niners I feel like are
one piece away. And I feel like I'm that
piece. So Ricky Pawall, Mike Evans,
Christian Kirk to go with George KD.
>> Not bad.
>> And CMC
in fact NFL.com because they can't stop
themselves. a list.
>> They have to put out the power rankings.
>> Yes.
>> In mid-March after free agency. Three of
the top five teams are in the NFC West.
One Seattle to the Rams. Now, number
five, the 49ers.
>> Don't love hearing that, Paul.
>> And if the Cardinals want some
motivation in the locker room, I'll save
you the scroll. Go all the way down.
That's where they have the Cardinals
right now before the draft. So, for
everything that has been said, and we
talked about this with Frank Sanders on
Red Sea Report, for all the talk and how
much is in the mailbag, I have no idea.
But 2026 for certain teams is all about
2027. Or so the narrative goes. Guess
what? That's not the way it goes in the
locker room.
>> Nope.
>> Look at how many guys are on one and
two-year deals. That's not the way it
works in the locker room. That is not
going to be the mentality in the locker
room. So, you can think that in some
sort of way as a as a fan that that's
the way it operates. This ain't the NBA.
That's not the way it goes. At least
from the inside out when you talk about
the locker room and how many of these
different players are in prove it years.
Well, and again, there's so many
different things, but yeah, I mean, look
at Max Crosby. That whole situation
>> recorded last Tuesday and then within
minutes probably after the podcast was
posted,
>> Baltimore backed out of the trade. I
mean, Max Crosby, the whole reason that
kind of got
messed up with the Raiders, which is
funny because now he's going to be
playing for the Raiders, it looks like,
is because they wanted to shut him down
and they wanted to tank for Fernando
Mendoza, which worked out well for them.
Um, yeah, that you're right, Paul. I
mean, players,
you know, if you go if you go into the
locker room this past season and you try
to talk to Trey McBride or Michael
Wilson or Buddha Baker or any of them
really,
they're not in a good mood
and they're not thinking to themselves,
well, this is going to be a good draft
pick. No one's ever It's It's really
annoying, actually. The number of fans
are like, let's you they should go tank.
Now, I I get the idea that, okay, if you
put together a poor roster, you're
probably going to But the problem in the
NFL especially, and I know it's a
year-to-year thing, but like if you have
a poor roster, you that that early draft
pick is only going to help you at one
position, whatever it might be, and then
you still have a poor roster.
>> Not to mention, look at this year as an
example. What if what if you quote
unquote tanked and you had the second
pick in the draft and it's like this
year where there is one quarterback to
take? It's not a guarantee.
>> I I'm also going to go back uh if you
recall, Paul, the fine 2011 season. Um
I would and and I'm not c saying he'd
ever listen to this podcast. He is local
and I know I've said things like this
before and he has been okay with it
because he has a lot of self-awareness.
So I prop him for that. But John Skelton
is not the quarterback Jacobe Brassette
is. Jacobe Brassette is a better
quarterback.
>> Absolutely. John Skelton was that
starter most of 2011 when that when the
Cardinals started one and seven and
you're thinking John Skelton then
they're going to end up with a top pick
and they ended up seven and nine I think
that year
>> and they should have been eight and
eight if Early Lucette doesn't drop a
touchdown pass in Cincinnati.
>> So that's right
>> I mean oh my gosh
>> you don't you don't know what's going to
happen this year. I mean they they they
could but I heard somebody talk about it
and I think this is true. Yes, they got
blown out way too many games. defense
really got sideways. And yes, they won a
couple of close games at the beginning
of the year, but there were a number of
close games they lost that like who
knows what happens on a year-to-year
basis. And if you win seven games,
you're not getting the number one pick.
We Andrew Wingard was sitting right
here. And we asked him about Cardinals
Jacksonville in that game. And he made
the game saving play for the Jags at the
very end obviously breaking up the
fourth down heave from Jacobe Brassette
to Xavier Weaver, which he was very
proud of. But he said going into the
game that he was reminding people in the
locker room, do not look at the record.
Look at some of the talent. Look at some
of the schemes. Sure enough, that was a
threepoint game against Jacksonville
more than halfway through the season.
But he talked about in the NFL how that
margins, unless you're an absolute
outlier like the Windless Lions a few
years ago, the margins are so small.
Twice in Jacksonville, they went from a
four- win team to the playoffs. He's
done it twice. Yeah,
>> they went from four wins last year to 13
wins. And he said it's just if you can
get the right leadership, if you can get
the right buy in, if you can stay
healthy. Now, I think there's two big
questions for the Cardinals right here,
right now going into the draft. One is
the right side of the offensive line.
What's your answer there? And then
number two, can you get another pass
rusher to go with Josh Sweat? I think
those are the two. And then presuming,
you know, James Connor is anywhere close
to what he's been in the past. I mean,
look at the running back room, how
competitive that's going to be. Tyler
Algier, who's a complete dog. Anybody
who's watched him, James Conor,
>> that's dog d a wg.
>> And and then to use that analogy,
Darren, uh to and then steal from Wolf,
you know, you get enough dogs in the
locker room, even the cats start
barking. What about Trey Benson? Trey
Benson's in a prove it year. He better
get on board and start channeling some
of his inner James Connor and Tyler
Algier. And obviously he has the skill
set and the measurables to do it with
finisher speed home run hitter terms of
the so right there for Jacobe Reset that
run game has to be so much better than a
year ago. Please tell us it's going to
be so much better than a year ago. And
if you can have a balanced offense
that's half the battle if you're Mike
Laflur coming into this year at least to
me. All right that's enough of a rant.
>> Uh yeah that was that was a quality one.
>> That was good though. I do want to hit
one and and Danny briefly talked about
the Max Crosby thing falling through. I
just this is always one of my favorite
parts of free agency is when fans hear
the name of somebody coming through and
then they get mad especially early on
why things aren't being announced and
everything and the Max Crosby thing
brings it all to the forefront.
Obviously that was a trade but there is
a reason why teams don't like announcing
stuff till they're official and that's
why the pending physical. Now, we can
argue all day of what exactly happened
with Max Crosby in particular, but
generally like I know the Cardinals,
they will not announce anything official
until the guy is past his physical and
signed on the dotted line. They don't
want to because of this exact thing. If
a guy if you think a guy's coming in and
he doesn't pass his physical, then it
just kind of looks sideways. Now, it's
kind of a moot point because all the
agents out there want to make sure that
everybody knows their guys are going to
a certain team. So they leak it to the,
you know, the shuffers and the Rapa
ports of the world anyways. But that's
why teams don't announce it ahead of
time is because they want that physical
past before they get ahead of
themselves.
>> It's got to, you know, it's got to cross
the finish line. It's got to break the
tape. What was the marathon just two
weeks ago? New York City Marathon, 26.2
2 miles and the American chased down the
leader on a final ridiculous kick over
the last half mile and won by 0.01
seconds over a 26 plus mile marathon. So
you got to wait for it to cross the
finish line. That's the moral of the
story.
>> So uh to kind of bring this full circle
like once you cross the finish line with
your water heater you'll feel better. Is
that
>> you'll start showering again?
>> Nothing you guys can say. I'm going to
leave it with this. Okay.
>> Was quite as insulting
as the wife and daughter leaving for
spring break
>> and not trusting and not not only
leaving without me
>> invite
>> not trusting me with Cheeto. [gasps]
>> They didn't trust me to take care of the
dog. They boarded the dog.
>> They're gone for 5 days
>> and they're like, "No, we don't trust
you with Cheeto." They boarded the dog.
>> I'm like, "What?
>> How insulted should I be?
I can't take care of a dog for 5 days.
>> You should be insulted.
>> Yes. Thank you.
>> First of all, aren't you like, why are
we paying for this dog to be boarded
instead of me take What do you mean?
Thank you. Like, don't you have control?
>> THAT'S MY POINT. NO, IT IT WAS ALREADY
DONE. He was gone before I knew it. I'm
like, well, where's Cheeto? You know,
I'm taking
>> We're not telling you what boarding
places.
>> You really need to step up how you're
taking care of Cheeto.
>> I'm taking I'm taking him to the
airport. I'm like, well, where's the
dog? And then
>> blame Cheeto for the water heater.
>> We We said we outsourced the dog care.
>> Wow. Wait, isn't your son home too on
spring break?
>> Yes. Yes. Yes. It can always get worse.
You're right, Darren.
>> Boy, nobody can nobody likes the men in
your family. Man,
>> that'll do it for this edition of
Cardinal Underground brought to you by
Pacific Office Automation.